Odzao Esther Lardze

Email | +233 543 920 766 <u>Linkedin</u> | <u>Github</u> Ghana, Kumasi

SUMMARY

Front end Developer with 2 years of experience in creating and maintaining websites. I am keen to use my knowledge and practical experience to contribute to innovative projects and collaborate with diverse teams in creating exceptional web applications. I embrace emerging technologies and constantly strive to seize opportunities that allow me to broaden my skill sets

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Dec 2023 – Feb 2024 Remote – Ecentials, Ghana

* Contributed to developing the hospital/pharmacy management system, that can track sales, withdrawals, deposits, and sales reports.

Frontend Developer(Intern)

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Remote - Zap Technologies, Kumasi, Ghana

- * Designed and developed dynamic and responsive web application using next Js, Tailwindcss, firebase
- * Managed and directed a team to achieve project goals, ensuring timely completion and high-quality deliverables

EDUCATION

KWAME NKRUMAH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Ghana 2020 – 2024

BSc. Computer Engineering

Remote

HOLBERTON SCHOOL Software Engineering

Feb 2022 - April 2023

CERTIFICATIONS

- * Alx Software Engineering
- * Introduction to Project Management
- * AWS cloud foundation

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, Typescript

Frameworks : Next.js, React js, TailwindCSS, Express Js

Database : MongoDB

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, Github

PROJECTS

Youtube clone Live app Source Code

· A clone version of youtube. A user can watch videos, search for personalized videos, and read commets.

p2p Tutoring Platform

Next js, Firebase, TailwindCSS

Source Code

· A peer to peer tutorng platform where students needing academic assistance can visit the platform and book their peers who are an expert to tutor them at a cost

Careari <u>Live app</u> <u>Source Code</u>

· A fully responsive frontend for job search portal ui with jobs based on categories.